[{"answer": "Well, every witness, starting with the opening statements, Piers, but every witness so far that's taken the stand, except for one lawyer, the defense has gotten Klein out there and today they really struck, if you will, from their standpoint.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "What exactly came out today?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "But the side effect of Demerol and the reason it's so significant is that it had a big impact on someone's ability to have a good sleep, right?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "A little intoxicated?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "It could fluctuate.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Estimate for us how many times a week you would do that, take him to Dr. Klein's office?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, yes, because what Jermaine Jackson -- his point was, and it's well taken, that audio recording that we heard in court was so dramatic.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "I mean are you still feeling as confident given that evidence today?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, this is what the prosecution really hammered on with both of the witnesses that were in the house and out of the house during that time where there was chaos.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Now why would he not do that?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "ARWICK: I have not taken to even watch this fiasco.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "What are your thoughts about it all?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I was at home.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Where were you when you heard that Michael had died?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I don't think so, no.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "How could it be -- is it possible that Michael could have been a drug addict without anyone around him who cared about him really knowing?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "What is your gut feeling, Dionne, tell you has gone down here?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "He was wonderful.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Very precocious.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Super confident boy?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Oh, undoubtedly.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Did you know from that stage, when you watched him, did you think he was going to turn out to be this extraordinarily gifted performer?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Unmistakably.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "He had a unique talent?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "You know, not for me it didn't.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Did any part of Michael, his story and everything, play into your thinking for you with this?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "And his growing years as a drummer and how he went on and on to play with some of the greats in our industry.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Exactly the intention.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Is that the intention?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I love that man.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Do you think he's going to win?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I would hope so.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "You're the most angry man in -- probably in the world, aren't you, Lewis?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "No, nothing will help.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "You want water?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Sarah Palin.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Who do you most fear becoming the Republican nominee on the basis they could then become president?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Because -- I don't think she exists.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "She doesn't exist.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What do you mean not exists?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, that's really what makes her superfiction.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "You couldn't invent someone like Sarah Palin, could you?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well, first off I don't know how many Americans.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Why is she able to resonate with so many Americans in a positive way?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "No, but I'm British.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Have you ever gotten a phone call from somebody asking you your opinion of anything?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Isn't she a female Lewis Black?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I think in part because they have listened to the Tea Party, to the point they've given a disproportion in amount of power much the way in the '60s when I was a kid in college.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Why has it become so angry?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Well, because they didn't sit down and talk to the Republicans and do whatever it is that the Republicans think that they wanted.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Why does that make you a bad president?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Because we -- I think we graduate kids who don't know how to add or subtract.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Why has the American business model gone so badly wrong so quickly?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "LACK: When -- there are moments like when they're going to tell me -- I know there are moments that are coming, when they say to me, \"Keeping up With The Kardashians\" is going off the air.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Do you ever have had moments of calm, quiet happiness?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I thought you were dying.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Why did you?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I'm so well, thank you.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Goldie, how are you?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "I swear to God.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Is it really?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Do gentlemen prefer blondes?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Well, 9/11 was sort of the catalyst, I guess you could say.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Why after 9/11?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I think that the one thing is they have to -- it isn't about children.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "What are the key things from this book that you think parents need to know about children, that perhaps they haven't thought about?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Well, the brain actually has a tremendous amount to do with it.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "How much of that creates this kind of anxiety to young people, do you think?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "No, they said don't get married, it's great.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Do they care?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "I think that getting back to some of the stuff I'm doing -- and I'm not really selling this, but it really all goes into the same theme -- is really emotional intelligence.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Does it just have a bad effect on people?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "I wouldn't call it depression.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Or are you now just this bubbly Goldie that we all assume you always are?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Very much.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Have you enjoyed being out of movies for 10 years?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "It's a comedy?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Here it is: it's a comedy but it actually -- the whole thing will be very deep and really -- but we have a lot of --", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "It's an HBO comedy series?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "Yes, I kind of am excited.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Are you excited to be getting back on the acting saddle?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Properly is really kind of the key.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "One of them is, how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I do love you.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Am I right in thinking husband number two at the moment is being relegated by the hour?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "It's just crazy.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "What a cool thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "No, I love that.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "But that's sort of an obvious, isn't it?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110928pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "Can we do it for longer next time?", "qSentId": 762}]